O.k., I'm Bobby Larew.
One of the drills you can do to work on your front entries is just called a line up.
A line up I'm going to do on the 3 meter board, o.k.
I do that because it gives me enough height and I don't have to worry about doing a good hurdle to practice a line up.
You can solely concentrate on the line up.
A good line up I'm going to go to the end of the board feet together, I'm going to bend at the waste and extend my arms.
What I'm concentrating on is making sure I get my hands closed above my head, make sure my elbows are locked, my biceps are squeezing my head and my ears.
Make sure I have no arch like I'm sucking my back this way; make sure I got my hips under me a little bit.
I want to have nice tight legs, thighs spread apart; leave it together, nice tight toe frame.
I shouldn't get a lot of splash.
I should go in vertical and I should be working on my pike save at the end.
So I'm going to go walk up to the 3 meter and do a front line up.